"Weaving For Victory: Weaving Today the Pattern of Tomorrow" TWUA Radio Scripts 6390
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
"Weaving For Victory: Weaving Today the Pattern of Tomorrow" TWUA Radio Scripts
1943-1984
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Textile Workers' Union of America (TWUA)
Scardino, Margaret
Ostrow, Alice Scardino
6390
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Transcripts, correspondence, news cliippings.
Collection contains scripts from the TWUA radio program "Weaving For Victory" which ran from May 1943 through December 1943.
8622705
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 02, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 08, 2015
Biographical / Historical
The Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA) was an union for textile workers originally established through the Congress of Industrial Oranizations in 1939. In 1976 it merged with the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America and became the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU).
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Scardino, Margaret; Ostrow, Alice Scardino; Textile Workers' Union of America (TWUA)
8622705
- Keir Jorgensen Correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Fred Muscheck's Report on the Program, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  To TWUA President Emil Rieve, August 12, 1943.
- Programs for May, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Programs for June, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Programs for July, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Programs for August, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Programs for September, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Programs for October, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Programs for November, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Program for December 6th, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  "Winding up the Program" Final broadcast of the series
- Philadelphia Textile Labor, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Newspaper, September 1943, Doak Special Election Issue
- CIO News: Joe Warworker, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Newspaper clipping, August 23, 1943. Cartoons highlighting the problems of workers on the home front